//questions to push into array
var questions = [];
questions.push({
  question: 'Who knocked out the Lakers in the 2006-2007 playoffs?',
  selection: ['Phoenix Suns', 'Denver Nuggets', 'San Antonio Spurs', 'Boston Celtics'],
  answer: 0
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Who ousted Elgin Baylorâ€™s 34.0 PPG to take the Scoring Title in 1962 by more than 10.0 PPG?',
  selection: ['Jerry West', 'Wilt Chamberlain', 'Bill Russell', 'Oscar Robertson'],
  answer: 1
});
questions.push({
  question: 'What year did the Lakers record their string of 33 consecutive wins?',
  selection: ['1990-1991', '1971-1972', '2000-2001', '1957-1958'],
  answer: 1
});
/*questions.push({
  question: 'Which Laker holds the franchise record for most steals in a single game?',
  selection: ['Magic Johnson', 'Elgin Baylor', 'Kobe Bryant', 'Jerry West'],
  answer: 1
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Which Laker does not have his number retired?',
  selection: ['Byron Scott', 'James Worthy', 'Elgin Baylor', 'Gail Goodrich'],
  answer: 0
});
questions.push({
  question: 'What year did James Worthy\'s number retired?',
  selection: ['1995', '2000', '2003', '1999'],
  answer: 0
});
questions.push({
  question: 'What number did Gail Goodrich have retired',
  selection: ['11', '22', '25', '30'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question: 'What year was Wilt Chamberlain\'s number retired as a Laker?',
  selection: ['1983', '1990', '1992', '1997'],
  answer: 0
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Which Laker holds the franchise record for most rebounds in a single quarter?',
  selection: ['Elgin Baylor', 'Shaquille O\'Neal', 'Wilt Chamberlain', 'Andrew Bynum'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question:'What team did Kobe Bryant outscore through 3 quarters in 2006?',
  selection: ['Toronto Raptors', 'Dallas Mavericks', 'Phoenix Suns', 'Denver Nuggets'],
  answer: 1
});
questions.push({
  question: 'How many times have the Lakers placed 1st in their division?',
  selection: ['22', '31', '29', '17'],
  answer: 1
});
questions.push({
  question:'What team did Kobe Bryant recorded an all time NBA record 12 3-pointers against?',
  selection: ['Seattle Supersonics', 'Toronto Raptors', 'LA Clippers', 'San Antonio Spurs'],
  answer: 1
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Wilt Chamberlain holds the franchise single season record of how many RPG',
  selection: ['14.7 RPG', '18.3 RPG', '21.1 RPG', '26.9 RPG'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Who knocked the Lakers out of the 2002-2003 NBA playoffs?',
  selection: ['Detroit Pistons', 'Minnesota Timberwolves', 'San Antonio Spurs', 'Houston Rockets'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Which Laker holds the franchise record for most points scored in a single season?',
  selection: ['Elgin Baylor', 'Magic Johnson', 'Kobe Bryant', 'Kareem Abdul-Jabbar'],
  answer: 2 
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Kareem Abdul-Jabbar holds the Lakers franchise record with ____ career blocks.',
  selection: ['1,599 Career Blocks', '1,781 Career Blocks', '2,012 Career Blocks', '2,694 Career Blocks'],
  answer: 3
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Which player was NOT drafted by the Lakers?',
  selection: ['Mark Madsen', 'Sasha Vujacic', 'Byron Scott', 'Elden Campbell'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question: 'Which Laker set the record for most points scored (61) in a single NBA finals game?',
  selection: ['Elgin Baylor', 'Jerry West', 'Kareem Abdul-Jabbar', 'Wilt Chamberlain'],
  answer: 0
});
questions.push({
  question: 'What year did the Lakers join the BAA?',
  selection: ['1937', '1942', '1948', '1951'],
  answer: 2
});
questions.push({
  question: 'How many years did Shaquille O\'Neal play as a Laker?',
  selection: ['10', '8', '6', '7'],
  answer: 1
});*/